ellinia.net 2015-12-13

# Privacy Policies and Legal Disclaimer | Ellinia - MapleStory Private Server

Thread Status:
     Not open for further replies.

  1. 

###  _**Staff Member**_ _**Supreme Leader**_

Joined:
    Oct 17, 2014

Messages:
    148

Likes Received:
    636

>   
>  **Our Commitment To Privacy**
> 
> Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from every page where personally identifiable information may be requested.
> 
> **The Information We Collect:**
> 
> This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Ellinia website. On some pages, you can make donations, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
> 
> Email Address  
>  IP Information  
>  Personal Information
> 
> **The Way We Use Information**
> 
> We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary when the law requires us to comply.
> 
> We use email addresses to answer the emails we receive, to verify upon registration, to send opt-in only contacts such as thread subscriptions and PM notifications. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
> 
> We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
> 
> **Advertising**
> 
> We also use third party advertisements support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example), showing certain ads based on specific sites visited or provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
> 
> Our website contains some affiliate marketing links, which means we get paid commission on sales of those products or services we write about. Our editorial content is not influenced by advertisers or affiliate partnerships. We use a 3rd Party to enable these affiliate partnerships. You can read their Privacy Policy and find more information on the cookies they use.
> 
> Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
> 
> **Our Commitment To Data Security**
> 
> To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
> 
> **Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**
> 
> Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. Upon registration all children under 13 are denied.
> 
> **Public Shaming Policy**
> 
> Anyone reversing donations to Ellinia are subject to a closed account and their **payment details and personal information placed directly into their signature for public viewing.** If you want to reverse a payment to Ellinia then go for it, but we will make sure you are named and shamed and the data will not be removed. **Your payment and personal details will be made public and searchable at Google. You have been warned.**
> 
> **How To Contact Us**
> 
> Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us via private message or by using the [Contact Us ](http://ellinia.net/misc/contact)form.
> 
> **Disclaimer**
> 
> **No warranties**
> 
> This website is provided "as is" without any representations or warranties, express or implied. The owner of this site makes no representations or warranties in relation to this website or the information and materials provided on this website.
> 
> **Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, the owner of this site does not warrant that:**
> 
> This website will be constantly available, or available at all; or the information on this website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.
> 
> Nothing on this website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind.
> 
> **Limitations of Liability**
> 
> The owner of this site will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contact, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this website:
> 
> to the extent that the website is available;  
>  for any indirect, special or consequential loss; or  
>  for any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated savings, loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information or data.
> 
> These limitations of liability apply even if the owner of this site has been expressly advised of the potential loss.
> 
> **Exceptions**
> 
> Nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit the owners liability in respect of any:
> 
> death or personal injury caused by the owner of this site's negligence;  
>  fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on the part of the owner of this site; or  
>  matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for the owner of this site to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.
> 
> **Reasonableness**
> 
> By using this website, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this website disclaimer are reasonable.
> 
> If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this website.
> 
> **Other Parties**
> 
> You accept that, as a limited liability entity, the owner of this site has an interest in limiting the personal liability of its officers and employees. You agree that you will not bring any claim personally against officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the website.
> 
> Without prejudice to the foregoing paragraph, you agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this website disclaimer will protect this sites officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors as well as the owner of this site.
> 
> **Unenforceable provisions**
> 
> If any provision of this website disclaimer is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that will not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this website disclaimer.
> 
> **This website disclaimer**
> 
> This website disclaimer is based on an original template created by website-contracts.co.uk and distributed by freenetlaw.com​

Takeoverkyle and Bear like this. 

Thread Status:
     Not open for further replies.
